AI coding agents can move fast.
Teams still need proof before apply.
ProofGate for Band
A multi-agent apply gate for AI code changes.
Band is the live coordination layer.
Each agent has one job.
Success path:
Human -> Intake -> Planner -> Engineer -> Tester -> Reviewer -> Human
Intake structures the request.
Planner scopes the change.
Engineer proposes the patch.
Tester validates behavior and scope.
Reviewer sends the proof packet to the human.
The output is not just code.
It is a proof packet.
Proof packet includes:
problem, impact, fix, simulated diff, validation, and safe_to_apply.
Failure path:
Reviewer -> Issue Isolator -> Reviewer -> Human
safe_to_apply: false
The dashboard shows transcript, proof packet, diff, validation, and decision.
18 tests passing.
Public GitHub repo ready.
ProofGate turns Band agent collaboration into an auditable human apply gate.